Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session two of unit four, it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you open the assessment booklet and
scroll down to section two, as you will
see, there are three learning objectives
and there are three questions to answer
to fulfill these learning objectives.
So for question one, it's asking
you to provide an explanation of
what is meant by malicious software.
So this is an explain question, so
you need to provide good detail.
So what is malicious software?
So think about the different
types of malicious software
and what it does and provide an
explanation in relation to those.
For question two, this
is an identify question.
So you can just list your responses
or bullet point your responses,
and it's asking you to identify
the different ways that malicious
software can infect the system.
So how is it done?
What are the different ways that malicious
software can get onto your system?
How did the cyber criminals
target you and the ways that they
utilise to infect your system.
And for question three, again, this is
an identify question, and it's asking you
to identify the different methods that
can be used to remove malicious software.
So think about how the various tools and
techniques that you can use to ensure
that software is removed from your system.
Once you've done that, check through your
answers, and if you're happy, proofread
them, run the spelling and grammar check,
and then you can save the assessment
booklet and move on to session three.